https://www.dbshoes.co.uk/pu+privacy-policy+privacy+1

Fitting
E-EEE (V)
EE
EE - 4E (2V)
4E
6E
6E - 8E (6V)
EE
EE - 4E (2V)
4E
6E
6E - 8E (6V)
Privacy
DB Shoes Ltd respects your right to privacy. This Privacy Policy sets out details of the information that we may collect from you and how we may use that information.
This Privacy Policy should be read alongside, and in addition to, our website Terms and Conditions (accessible on this page Please read this Privacy Policy carefully - by using this website (the "Website") or purchasing any of our products, you agree to its terms (including as amended from time to time). If, for any reason, you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please stop using the Website immediately.
Who are we?
In this Privacy Policy, references to "we" or "us" are to DB Shoes Limited, a company incorporated in England and Wales (registered number 163960) whose registered office is at Irchester Road Rushden Northants NN10 9XF.
If you have any questions about how we collect, store and use your information, you may contact us by telephoning +44 (0)1933 359217 or by e-mailing us at enquiry@dbshoes.co.uk.
Our legal obligations
We will at all times only collect and process your personal information in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998, the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 and any other applicable data protection legislation.
Information Collection and Use
When you use the Website or contact us by post, telephone, fax or e-mail we may collect, store and use certain personal information that you disclose to us.
The information that we may collect from you may include your name, address, telephone, fax, e-mail and mobile contact details, details of any purchases that you make. We do not store any credit or debit card details. If you pay by credit or debit card through our web site or by telephone when payment is requested you are linked directly to the card processor through a secure payment gateway. We do not hold any of your card details. If you send an order through the post with your card details we shred the order once it is processed and payment is taken through a direct link to the card processor as though it was a telephone order. We may also collect details of your computer's internet protocol address and details of the web pages visited, which is automatically collected by our web server (see Cookies below).
How do we use your information?
By using the Website or purchasing any product through the Website, you agree that your information may be used by us, and by carefully selected third parties chosen by us for any of the following:
to customise the site according to individual selections in order to provide you with a personalised browsing experience;
to send you details (by post, phone, fax or e-mail) of other products or services which we think may be may interest you unless you inform us that you do not wish your information to be used in this manner either by ticking the appropriate box when registering or subsequently informing us in writing that you want to be removed from our database.
to send to you our email alerts. Such alerts will only be sent to you if you have requested us to send you e-mail alerts and will relate to the services on our Website for which you have expressed interest.
Log Files and cookies
We use IP addresses and details of pages visited to analyse trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.
The Website uses cookies. Cookies are small files stored on your computer's hard drive which are used to collect your personal information. You may choose to refuse cookies but, if you do so, some of the functionality of the Website may not longer be available to you.
For more information about cookies, including further details as to what they are and how to refuse them, please visit www.allaboutcookies.org.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that DB Shoes Limited is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. You should be aware of this when you leave our site and you should read the privacy statements of these third party sites. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Website.
Surveys & Contests
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose any information requested. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and delivery address), and demographic information (such as postcode, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the functionality of the site.
Security
We have put in place technical and organisational security measures to prevent the loss or unauthorised access of your personal information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. However, whilst we have used our best efforts to ensure the security of your data, please be aware that we cannot guarantee the security of information transmitted over the Internet.
If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to enquiry@dbshoes.co.uk.
Correcting, Updating and Removing Personal Information
You have the right to contact us in order to find out what information we hold about you [(please note that a £10 fee will be payable)] or to access, cancel or correct any information that we hold about you.
If any of your information changes or is incorrect, or if you no longer desire our service, we will correct, update or remove the personal data. This can be done either at your personal profile page or by sending us an email to enquiry@dbshoes.co.uk.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to update or amend our privacy policy, we will post reference to those changes on our Homepage. By continuing to use the Website or buying products from us you agree to be bound by the terms of any such update and/or amendment.
If at any point we wish to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you by email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
This policy was last updated on 01st July 2016.
Wider Fit Shoes Main Navigation
Privacy
Privacy
Contact Us
Contact Us
Sitemap
Sitemap
Privacy
Privacy
Contact Us
Contact Us
Sitemap
Sitemap
Printed from Wider Fit Shoes Website. https://www.dbshoes.co.uk ©Wider Fit Shoes
By using this site, you consent to our use of cookies. To learn more, please click here to view our Privacy Policy, or click here to close this message.
Total Qty:
0
View Shopping Basket
